Leah Nipatvaranan.

+61 4105 888 47

leah.sornsawan@gmail.com

Melbourne 3000

Summary

I'm focused on creating meaningful experiences through design.

I enjoy learning and solving problems. As I always seek inspiration on simple and clean design, tidying up things in the digital world is a passion. I specialize in Figma and Adobe XD and Photoshop.

Technical

UX Research

Understanding problem of users by collecting data and analysis process

UI Prototyping

Building wireframes and prototypes based on user journey mapping and user flows

Information Architecture

Structuring site content and functionality to reduce complexity of information

Interaction Design

Generatir	ıg
exception	ıal
interactio	n
experienc	es on
mobile an	d web

Visual Design

Creating styleguide
with accessible
color, icon, strong
layout and
typography

Usability Testing

Conducting user testing by providing scenario to collect feedback for improvement

Career

Event Assistant

Sidekicker

2019-Presents / Melbourne, VIC

- → Supporting the events manager with logistical and administrative support
- → Coordinating with venue staff to ensure that facilities are properly set up for an event
- → Recording attendance at events by scanning tickets or checking names against a list of registered guests
- → Setting up tables and chairs for events, as well as other tasks such as dusting or repairing broken items

Food and Service assistant

Baptcare

2020 / Melbourne, VIC

- → Delivering food from the kitchen to guests at the table or to a selfservice area
- → Greeting guests as they arrive at the venue, directing guests to tables, providing menus and taking orders
- → Setting up marquees, arranging tables and assisting with the preparation of event spaces
- → Assisting Chefs by washing vegetables, assembling sandwiches, sourcing ingredients from the stock room or plating up dishes
- → Adhere to all relevant health department rules/regulations and all customer service guidelines

Casual Japanese interpreter

H.I.S. International Tours.Inc

2018 / Bangkok, THAILAND

- → Translate messages, live speeches, voice recordings and documents into another language, with careful attention to providing proper context, meaning, tone and technical wording
- → Collaborate with colleagues to compile helpful information, including terms and definitions, into an organized glossary for regular reference during the translation process
- → Identify terms and words with conflicting meanings to determine which alternative provides clarity and reflects the original purpose of the message

Hall Staff

Noku Hotel Cafe

2016-2017 / Kyoto, JAPAN

- → Promptly address customer service issues and refer customers to management when necessary
- → Cooperate and communicate with all serving and kitchen staff
- → Handle complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives within the time limits, and follow up to ensure resolution

Education

Monash University UX / UI design

2022 / Melbourne, VIC

Assumption University Bacherlor of Arts in Business Japanese

2013-2018 / Bangkok, THAILAND

Ryukoku University International studies

2016-2017 / Kyoto, JAPAN